(Priya:)And for years,
everyone in my family
was convinced that he was
the clarinet enthusiast.
(Priya:)Hmm. What's that
piece of tape?
(Leonard:)Oh, that one doesn't
apply to you. You sit.
(Sheldon:)Hey.
Hey. How's it going?
(Leonard:)Not too bad. Did you hear
about Howard and Bernadette?
'Course I heard about it.
How did you hear about it?
(Penny:)I heard about it
from Sheldon.
(Leonard:)He got it from Amy.
Oh, damn it.
(Penny:)I told Amy that in the
strictest confidence.
(Penny:)Boy, some people are
such blabbermouths.
(Penny:)Well, whatever.
(Penny:)I'm sure Bernadette
can do better.
(Leonard:)Do you think a sexually ambivalent
Indian astrophysicist
(Leonard:)with selective mutism
and alcohol issues is better than
(Leonard:)a hundred-pound Jewish guy
who lives with his mom?
(Penny:)You are kidding.
Raj likes Bernadette?
I didn't say Raj.
Who said Raj?
(Penny:)Okay, give.
(Penny:)How do you know?
Did he tell you?
(Dr. Brian Greene:)No.
Well, then who?
(Leonard:)I can't say...
(Penny:)Priya told you.
What a little gossip.